# RYAN RUSTYN

707-696-9506 ryanrustyn@gmail.com

Santa Rosa, CA

#### **PROFILE**

Friendly but driven, looking at make a career change into tech. Spent much of the last 10 years working in horticulture developing strong skills in communication, and organization. Highly-adaptable, quick learner with a passion for technology.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Horticulturalist, Dirt Bag Farm; Santa Rosa, CA — 2020 - Present

- Manage and plan large work days; efficiently organizing work and assigning tasks; constantly questioning and developing new methods to speed up work flow
- Install and troubleshoot all automation and networking for the company

# Technician, MILWright; Sebastopol, CA — 2018-2019

- Assessed quality control problems and adjusted manufacturing processes to fix issues and produce quality products
- Worked with electrical and machinery, building and installing control units for hydraulic presses

# Tutor, Santa Rosa Junior College; Santa Rosa, CA — 2017-2018

 Worked with a variety of students teaching math and science helping meet each students learning needs

Horticulturalist, Private Clients; Santa Rosa, CA — 2012-2017

### **EDUCATION**

Santa Rosa Junior College, Santa Rosa, CA - Electrical Engineering

### **SKILLS**

• Problem Solving, Mathematics, Collaborative, Adaptability, Communication